Guide to Barbara Sloan European Union Document Collection, 1951-2004 EUDC
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- POLICY AREA, II.
  - INTERNATIONAL COMMODITIES & AGREEMENTS, 17.
    - MANUFACTURED PRODUCTS
      - Agricultural Machinery, World [6(CST 712)(1)], 1964-1989; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 388)
      - Aircraft, World [6(CST 734)(1)], 1970-1997; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 389)
      - Aluminum, World [6(CST 684)(1)], 1966-1994; 3.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 388)
      - Beverages, Europe [6(CST 11)(20)], 1966-1980; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 384)
      - Cement, World [6(CST 661.2)(1)], 1967-1984; 5.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 388)
      - Chemicals, World [6(CST 5)(1)], 1969-1985; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 383)
      - Electronic Industry, World [6(CST 72)(1)], 1966-1999; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 388)
      - Fertilizers, World [6(CST 56)(1)], 1967-1982; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 385)
      - Floor Coverings, Rugs, Tapestries, World [6(CST 657)(1)], 1967; 9.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 388)
      - Glass, World [6(CST 664)(1)], 1962-1987; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 388)
      - Motor Vehicles, Europe [6(CST 732)(20)], 1966-2003; 11.; 2 folders 8"
      - Motor Vehicles, Europe [6(CST 732)(20)], 1966-2003; 12.; 2 folders 8" (Box 389)
      - Paper & Board, World [6(CST 25)(1)], 1965-1985; 13.; 1 folder 1" (Box 385)
      - Steel, Europe [6(CST 67)(20)], 1963-1985; 14.; 1 folder 1" (Box 388)
      - Steel, United States [6(CST 67)(103)], 1957-1984; 15.; 1 folder 1" (Box 388)
      - Steel, World [6(CST 67)(1)], 1957-1981; 16.; 1 folder 1" (Box 388)
      - Textiles, World [6(CST 65)(1)], 1969-2003; 17.; 7 folders 31" (Box 385, Box 386, Box 387, Box 388)
  - JUSTICE & HOME AFFAIRS, 18.
    - JUSTICE AND HOME AFFAIRS - General
      - JUSTICE AND HOME AFFAIRS - General [4423], 1993-2004; 1.; 1 folder 3" (Box 367)
    - CITIZEN AND HUMAN RIGHTS
      - Human & Fundamental Rights [342.7], 1976-2002; 1.; 3 folders 16" (Box 21)
      - Citizens' Rights, Pre Maastricht [420.6] (folder missing), 2. (Box 55)
      - Citizens' Rights, Justice and Home Affairs [4423.2], 1991-2003; 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 368)
    - POLICE COOPERATION
      - Terrorism [323.28], 1976-2004; 1.; 1 folder 3" (Box 7)
      - Trevi Group Official Meetings on Terrorism [433.3], 1985-1993; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 89)
      - Europol [4423.1], 1993-2003; 3.; 1 folder 3" (Box 368)
      - Criminal matters, Extradition, Organized Crime, Drug and Sex Trade [4423.3], 1996-2003; 4.; 1 folder 7" (Box 368)
    - BORDER CONTROLS
      - Immigration Policy, General [4423.4], 1995-2004; 1.; 1 folder 5" (Box 369)
      - Visa Rules [4423.41], 1995-2003; 2.; 1 folder 3" (Box 369)
      - Asylum [4423.42], 1995-2003; 3.; 1 folder 3" (Box 369)
      - Passport, EU [4423.43], 1974-2002; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 369)
      - Schengen Agreement [443.124], 1990-2003; 5.; 1 folder 5" (Box 187)
  - NEW TECHNOLOGIES - INFORMATION SOCIETY, 19.
    - Information Management [4413.3], 1971-2001; 1.; 1 folder 3" (Box 312)
    - EURONET/Information & Documentation Program [4413.33], 1977-1996; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 313)
    - Information Market, Special Program [4413.331], 1983-1994; 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 313)
    - Data Processing Research Program [4413.332], 1982-1996; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 313)
    - Data Exchange for the Agricultural Market - CADDIA [4413.34], 1984-2002; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 313)
    - Information System, Inter-institutional Integrated Services INSIS [4413.35], 1981-2003; 6.; 1 folder 1" (Box 313)
    - Information Delivery Systems [4413.36], 1978-2003; 7.; 4 folders 14" (Box 314)
    - Electronic Commerce [4413.361], 1966-2003; 8.; 1 folder 2" (Box 315)
  - REGIONAL POLICY, 20.
    - REGIONAL POLICY General [4416], 1983-2002; 1.; 1 folder 4" (Box 350)
    - Regional Community Programs [4416.1], 1965-2003; 2.; 4 folders 17" (Box 350)
    - European Regional Development Funds - Structural Funds [4416.11], 1973-2002; 3.; 5 folders 18" (Box 351, Box 352)
    - Regional Policy Committee [4416.12], 1975-1996; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 353)
    - Committee of the Regions [4416.2], 1993-2003; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 353)
    - Regional National Programs [4416.4], 1967-1998; 6.; 1 folder 3" (Box 353)
    - Urban Development [711.4], 1967-2003; 7.; 1 folder 4" (Box 408)
  - RESEARCH AND TECHNOLOGY, 21.
    - RESEARCH & TECHNOLOGY General
      - RESEARCH & TECHNOLOGY General [4412], 1975-2002; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 304)
      - Scientific & Technology Policy [4412.1], 1960-2003; 2.; 6 folders 30" (Box 304, Box 305, Box 306, Box 307)
      - Committee on Scientific & Technical Research (CREST) [4412.11], 1975-1995; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 307)
      - European Science Foundation [4412.12], 1974-2002; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 307)
      - Scientific & Technical Committees [4412.13], 1967-2000; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 307)
      - Scientific Technical & Nuclear Affairs, International Aspects [441.4], 1959-2003; 6.; 2 folders 5" (Box 165)
    - JOINT RESEARCH CENTERS General
      - JOINT RESEARCH CENTERS General [4415], 1968-2002; 1.; 2 folders 9" (Box 349)
      - Joint Research Center, Geel [4415.4], 1970-1980; 2.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 350)
      - Joint Research Center, Ispra [4415.1], 1959-1996; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 349)
      - Joint Research Center, Karlsruhe [4415.3], 1960-1988; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 350)
      - Joint Research Center, Petten [4415.2], 1961-2002; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 349)
    - NUCLEAR RESEARCH
      - European Atomic Energy Community (EURATOM) Situation [4412.2], 1966-2002; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 307)
      - Nuclear Research and Technology Programs [4412.21], 1960-2002; 2.; 2 folders 5" (Box 307)
      - Nuclear Installations [4412.211], 1958-2003; 3.; 1 folder 5" (Box 308)
      - Fusion Program Joint European Torus [4412.212], 1970-2002; 4.; 2 folders 6" (Box 309)
      - Nuclear Industry, Joint Enterprises [4412.213], 1961-2002; 5.; 1 folder 2" (Box 309)
    - NON-NUCLEAR RESEARCH
      - Non-Nuclear Research & Technology Programs [4412.22], 1969-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 309)
      - Agricultural Research [63.001.5], 1972-2003; 2.; 1 folder 4" (Box 402)
      - Biology Program Biotechnology [4412.221], 1970-2003; 3.; 2 folders 13" (Box 309)
      - Community Bureau of Reference (CBR) [4412.222], 1969-1997; 4.; 1 folder 2" (Box 310)
      - Data Processing Research Program [4413.332], 1982-1996; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 313)
      - European Coal and Steel Community (ECSC) Research Programs [456.63], 1958-2003; 6.; 3 folders 14" (Box 372)
      - Energy Research Programs [4417.12], 1975-2003; 7.; 5 folders 23" (Box 356)
      - Environmental Research & Studies [628.001.5], 1978-2001; 8.; 2 folders 6" (Box 395)
      - Non-Nuclear Research & Technology Programs [4412.22], 1969-2003; 9.; 1 folder 2" (Box 309)
      - Raw Materials, Research and Development for [338.11], 1977-1992; 10.; 1 folder 2" (Box 13)
      - Scientific & Technical Research (CDST), European Cooperation in the Field of [4412.223], 1973-2003; 11.; 1 folder 2" (Box 310)
      - Space Research [629.19], 1965-2004; 12.; 1 folder 5" (Box 402)
    - TECHNOLOGY
      - Technological operations – R&D [4412.3], 1969-1998; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 310)
      - Business Register Interoperability Throughout Europe (BRITE) [4412.31], 1985-1992; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 311)
      - European Strategic Program on Research in Information Technology (ESPRIT) and Microtechnology [4412.32], 1980-1997; 3.; 2 folders 9" (Box 311)
      - Technology Social impact [4412.33], 1981-2003; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 312)
      - Artificial Intelligence; Basic Research in Adapative Intelligence and Neurocomputing (BRAIN) [4412.34], 1987-1992; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 312)
      - EUREKA -Joint EC-EFTA Programs [4412.35], 1985-1999; 6.; 1 folder 2" (Box 312)
      - Research, Instruction Training Basic Research [4412.4], 1971-2003; 7.; 1 folder 2" (Box 312)
      - Technological Forecasts; Forecasting & Assessment in Science & Technology (FAST) [4412.5], 1974-1994; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 312)
  - SOCIAL AFFAIRS, 22.
    - SOCIAL AFFAIRS General
      - SOCIAL AFFAIRS General [445], 1960-2003; 1.; 6 folders 19" (Box 208, Box 209, Box 210)
    - DEMOGRAPHICS
      - Demography & Population [312], 1968-2003; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 6)
      - Youth in Europe [3.053.3(20)], 1965-2003; 2.; 3 folders 8" (Box 2)
      - Women in Europe [3.055.2(20)], 1968-2002; 3.; 2 folders 7" (Box 3)
    - SOCIAL ASPECTS OF TRANSPORT
      - Transport, Social Affairs in [445: 385/388], 1963-2002; 1.; 2 folders 9" (Box 210)
      - Transport, Consultative Committees for Social Affairs in [445: 385/388.1], 1972-1995; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 211)
    - ADJUSTMENT ASSISTANCE
      - European Social Fund [438], 1959-2002; 1.; 4 folders 15" (Box 92)
      - Readaptation, Reemployment General [445.01], 1968-1999; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 211)
      - Readaptation, Programs [445.011], 1969-1996; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 211)
      - Reconversion & Regional Policy, Social Aspects of [445.012], 1967-2001; 4.; 1 folder 1" (Box 211)
    - EDUCATION - VOCATIONAL TRAINING
      - Education in Europe [37(20)], 1958-2003; 1.; 5 folders 23" (Box 26, Box 27, Box 28)
      - Study of European Affairs [37(20)A], 1965-1978; 2.; 1 folder 6" (Box 28)
      - Scholarships [378.34], 1970-1982; 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 28)
      - Vocational Training [445.1], 1961-2003; 4.; 3 folders 10" (Box 211)
      - Vocational Training, Consultative Committee for [445.11], 1964-2003; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 212)
      - Vocational Training, European Centre for the Development of [445.12], 1974-2001; 6.; 1 folder 2" (Box 212)
      - European Training Foundation [445.13], 1994-2003; 7.; 1 folder 1" (Box 212)
    - LABOR MARKET
      - Manpower [445.2], 1960-2003; 1.; 2 folders 6" (Box 212)
      - Employment [445.21], 1967-2003; 2.; 6 folders 35" (Box 213, Box 214, Box 215)
      - Employment, Permanent Committee on [445.211], 1971-2002; 3.; 1 folder 3" (Box 215)
      - Free Movement for EC Nationals [445.22], 1960-2004; 4.; 5 folders 18" (Box 215, Box 216)
      - Free Movement of Workers, Consultative Committee for [445.221], 1963-2001; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 217)
      - Free Movement of Workers, Technical Committee for [445.222] (folder missing), 6. (Box 217)
      - European Coordination Office [445.223], 1982 & 1987; 7.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 217)
      - Exchange of Young Workers (Article 50) [445.23], 1969-2001; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 217)
      - Labor Relations & Working Conditions [445.3], 1970-2002; 9.; 1 folder 2" (Box 217)
      - Working Conditions [445.31], 1972-2003; 10.; 2 folders 11" (Box 217)
      - Labor Law [445.31], 1972-2003; 11.; 2 folders 11" (Box 217)
      - Consultation of Workers, Vredling proposal [445.311], 1978-2002; 12.; 1 folder 5" (Box 218)
      - Salaries & Income [445.32], 1960-1999; 13.; 1 folder 2" (Box 219)
      - Equal Pay, Salaries Article 119 [445.321], 1962-2003; 14.; 3 folders 9" (Box 219)
      - Labor Relations [445.33], 1964-1984; 15.; 1 folder 1" (Box 220)
      - Discrimination [445.34], 1999-2003; 16.; 2 folders 11" (Box 220)
    - SOCIAL SECURITY
      - Social Security [445.4], 1960-2003; 1.; 2 folders 11" (Box 220)
      - Social Security for Migrant EC Nationals [445.41], 1958-2003; 2.; 4 folders 17" (Box 220, Box 221)
    - SOCIAL SERVICES
      - Social Services & Housing, General [445.5], 1972-2002; 1.; 1 folder 1" (Box 222)
      - Social Services [445.51], 1960-2003; 2.; 1 folder 6" (Box 222)
      - Housing [445.52], 1964-2003; 3.; 1 folder 2" (Box 222)
      - Poverty Programs [445.53], 1975-2002; 4.; 1 folder 5" (Box 222)
      - European Foundation for Improvement of Living & Working Conditions (Eurofound) [445.6], 1973-2001; 5.; 1 folder 4" (Box 223)
    - HEALTH
      - Health Protection (Nuclear Contamination) [445.7], 1960-1993; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 223)
      - Nuclear Hygiene & Medicine [445.71], 1966-2003; 2.; 1 folder 1" (Box 223)
      - Radioactive Waste & Nuclear Safety Measures [445.72], 1970-2003; 3.; 3 folders 13" (Box 224)
      - Basic Standards - (European Atomic Energy Community) Euratom [445.73], 1959-2002; 4.; 1 folder 4" (Box 224)
      - Industrial Safety Health & Medicine [445.8], 1974-2003; 5.; 1 folder 6" (Box 225)
      - Public Health & Medicine [445.81], 1970-2004; 6.; 5 folders 24" (Box 225, Box 226)
      - Narcotics Policy [445.811], 1969-2003; 7.; 1 folder 5" (Box 227)
      - Drugs, Substance Abuse Policy [445.811], 1969-2003; 8.; 1 folder 5" (Box 227)
      - European Monitoring Centre for Drugs and Drug Addiction (EMCDDA) [445.812], 1994-2001; 9.; 1 folder 1" (Box 227)
      - Plant Safety (Except Nuclear Coal & Steel) [445.82], 1967-2003; 10.; 3 folders 17" (Box 227)
      - Agency for Health and Safety at Work [445.821], 1994-2003; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 228)
      - Working Conditions and Safety Problems in the Coal and Steel Sector [445.83], 1969-1997; 12.; 1 folder 1" (Box 228)
      - Mines Safety Commission [445.84], 1969-2003; 13.; 1 folder 1" (Box 228)
      - European Social Budget [445.9], 1974-1982; 14.; 1 folder 1" (Box 228)
  - TRANSPORT, 23.
    - TRANSPORT General
      - TRANSPORT General [447], 1960-2003; 1.; 1 folder 2" (Box 277)
    - TRANSPORT SECTORS
      - Railways [385], 1966-2003; 1.; 3 folders 13" (Box 32)
      - Transport, Containers [385/388], 1968-2002; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 33)
      - Inland Waterways and Canals [386], 1961-2003; 3.; 2 folders 6" (Box 33)
      - Sea Transport Shipping Ports Docks & Harbors [387], 1977-2003; 4.; 4 folders 21" (Box 33, Box 34, Box 35)
      - European Maritime Safety Agency [387.01], 2002-2003; 5.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 35)
      - Road Transport - Roads & Bridges [388.1], 1962-2003; 6.; 3 folders 14" (Box 35)
      - Tunnels [388.2], 1971-2002; 7.; 1 folder 2" (Box 36)
      - Pipelines [388.5], 1960-1998; 8.; 1 folder 1" (Box 36)
      - Air Transport [388.9], 1964-2003; 9.; 6 folders 31" (Box 37, Box 38, Box 39)
      - Eurocontrol [388.91], 1969-2003; 10.; 1 folder 1" (Box 39)
      - Airbus Including Dispute with U.S. [388.92], 1980-2002; 11.; 1 folder 2" (Box 39)
      - Aviation Safety Agency, European [388.93], 2003; 12.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 39)
    - TRANSPORT POLICY
      - Transport Policy & Access to the Market, General Development of [447.1], 1960-2003; 1.; 4 folders 15" (Box 277)
      - Transport, Objectives & Programs [447.11] (folder missing), 2. (Box 278)
      - Transport, Access to the Market [447.14], 1967-2003; 3.; 1 folder 6" (Box 278)
      - Consultative Committee on Transport [447.15], 1958-1986; 4.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 280)
    - TARIFF POLICY
      - Transport, Rates & Conditions [447.2], 1962-2003; 1.; 1 folder 4" (Box 279)
      - Transport, General Tariff Policy [447.21], 1963-2001; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 279)
      - Bureau des Tarifs [447.22] (folder missing), 3. (Box 279)
      - Transport, Special Provisions of the EEC Treaty for [447.23], 1997; 4.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 279)
      - Transport, Special Provisions of the ECSC Treaty for [447.24], 1954-2001; 5.; 1 folder 1" (Box 279)
    - INFRASTRUCTURE
      - Transport Infrastructure, Harmonization Coordination and Financial System for [includes information on Trans-European Networks (T-ENs) [447.3], 1960-2003; 1.; 1 folder 4" (Box 279)
      - Transport, Harmonization of Provisions Affecting Competition in [447.31], 1963-1997; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 280)
      - Transport Infrastructure Investments, Technical Harmonization & Coordination of [447.32], 1990-2003; 3.; 1 folder 4" (Box 280)
      - Transport Infrastructure Costs, Financial System for [447.33], 1963-2003; 4.; 1 folder 4" (Box 280)
    - INTERNATIONAL ASPECTS
      - Transport, Contracts and International Conventions Relating to All Modes of [447.4], 1971-2003; 1.; 1 folder 4" (Box 281)
- MISCELLANEOUS, III.
  - Communication Theory Mass Media [007], 1966, 1986; 1.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 1)
  - Newspapers Journalism [07], 1965-2000; 2.; 1 folder 2" (Box 1)
  - Religion & European Integration [2: 420], 1953-2003; 3.; 1 folder 1" (Box 1)
  - Farm Organizations, US [301.188: 63(103)], 1964-1992; 4.; 1 folder 3" (Box 3)
  - Statistics, Miscellaneous [31], 1963-2003; 5.; 1 folder 3" (Box 4)
  - Economic Indicators, General [31: 338.97], 1963-2003; 6.; 1 folder 3" (Box 4)
  - Statistical Method Theory [311], 1965-2003; 7.; 2 folders 7" (Box 6)
  - Political Science, Europe: Education [32(20)], 1963-1985; 8.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 6)
  - Policies Towards Developing Countries [327(10: 4)], 1969, 1970, 1981; 9.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 8)
  - Political Parties [329], 1961-2003; 10.; 1 folder 4" (Box 8)
  - Brain Drain [331.62: 62.001.5], 1967-1980; 11.; 1 folder 1" (Box 8)
  - Holidays Vacation Leave [available to public] see 394 [331.817], 1968-2001; 12.; 1 folder 1" (Box 8)
  - Labor Productivity [331.87], 1977-1987; 13.; 1 folder 2" (Box 8)
  - Banks & Banking Practice General [332.1(20)], 1971-2001; 14.; 1 folder 2" (Box 9)
  - Savings Banks [332.2], 1964-1991; 15.; 1 folder 3" (Box 10)
  - Eurodollars [332.433], 1963-1991; 16.; 1 folder 2" (Box 10)
  - International Monetary Systems & Problems [332.453.2], 1964-1999; 17.; 1 folder 4" (Box 11)
  - International Liquidity [332.453.21], 1961-1990; 18.; 1 folder 2" (Box 11)
  - Balance of Payments: United States [332.453.23(103)], 1963-2000; 19.; 1 folder 2" (Box 11)
  - Foreign Investment of the United States [332.67(103)], 1964-2001; 20.; 1 folder 3" (Box 12)
  - Foreign Investment in the United States [332.67(103) A], 1976-2001; 21.; 1 folder 2" (Box 12)
  - Tax Systems - Taxes [336.2], 1969-1997; 22.; 1 folder 1" (Box 12)
  - Tax Systems - Taxes - United States [336.2(103)], 1969, 1982; 23.; 1 folder 1" (Box 12)
  - Public Expenditure [336.5], 1969-1979; 24.; 1 folder 3 documents (Box 12)
  - Free Trade Protection - Customs (Trade Controls) [337], 1963-1981; 25.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 12)
  - Import Restrictions, General [337.37], 1968-1984; 26.; 1 folder 1" (Box 12)
  - Export Subsidies - Measures of Fiscal Aid General [337.4], 1971; 1972; 27.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 12)
  - Drawback International Trade [337.41], 1969; 28.; 1 folder 1 document (Box 12)
  - US Chamber of Commerce International Operations [338.72], 1977-1985; 29.; 1 folder 1" (Box 14)
  - Concentration - Monopolies [338.8], 1968-1986; 30.; 1 folder 1" (Box 14)
  - Economic Situation United States [338.97(103)], 1968-1981; 31.; 1 folder 1" (Box 14)
  - Economic Forecasts General [338.971], 1970-1985; 32.; 1 folder 1" (Box 14)
  - Agricultural Policy World [338.98: 63(1)], 1968, 1974; 33.; 1 folder 2 documents (Box 14)
  - Agricultural Policy United States [338.98: 63(103)], 1969-1989; 34.; 1 folder 1" (Box 14)
  - State Aid, Agricultural General [338.983: 63], 1971-1983; 35.; 1 folder 5" (Box 14)
  - Economic Planning [338.984.3], 1962-1980; 36.; 1 folder 1" (Box 14)
  - Technical Assistance and Aid - World [338.984.5(1)], 1970-1993; 37.; 1 folder 1" (Box 14)
  - Standard of Living; Purchasing Power [339.452], 1964-1986; 38.; 1 folder 3" (Box 16)
  - Summit Conferences G-7, G-8 (420 C for EC Summit Conferences) [341.18], 1975-2002; 39.; 2 folders 9" (Box 18)
  - Franco-German Treaty of Cooperation (also called Treaty of Friendship and Elysee Treaty) [341.24(49: 42)], 1964-1998; 40.; 1 folder 1" (Box 20)
  - Law, International Criminal [341.4], 1971-2003; 41.; 1 folder 2" (Box 20)
  - Law, Private International [341.5], 1979-2002; 42.; 1 folder 1" (Box 20)
  - Electoral Law - Electoral Systems [342.8], 1968-2003; 43.; 1 folder 3" (Box 23)
  - Public Works [351.712], 1968-1996; 44.; 1 folder 0.5"
  - Identity Cards General [351.755.62], 1968-1989; 45.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 24)
  - Passports Visas Foreigners Aliens General [351.756], 1977-1998; 46.; 2 folders 5" (Box 24)
  - Municipalities & Local Authorities [352], 1962-2003; 47.; 1 folder 1" (Box 24)
  - Governmental Information Services & Policies [354.36], 1964-1983; 48.; 1 folder 1" (Box 24)
  - Insurance, United States [368(103)], 1976-1977; 49.; 1 folder 1-3 documents (Box 25)
  - Insurance, Europe [368(20)], 1968-1980; 50.; 1 folder 1" (Box 25)
  - Education in the United States [37(103)], 1966; 1998; 51.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 28)
  - Distribution of Merchandise [381], 1968-1999; 52.; 1 folder 1" (Box 29)
  - International Trade [382], 1968-1999; 53.; 1 folder 3" (Box 29)
  - Agriculture, International Trade (Problems & Theory) [382: 63], 1963-2002; 54.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 30)
  - Agricultural Trade Policy - United States [382.14: 63(103)], 1967-1992; 55.; 2 folders 3" (Box 30)
  - Trade Policy United States Parts I & II [382.14(103)], 1961-1977; 56.; 4 folders 14" (Box 30)
  - Committee for a National Trade Policy [382.14(103): 061.2], 1960-1968; 57.; 1 folder 1" (Box 31)
  - Standardization, General - Harmonization of standards [389.6], 1969-1999; 58.; 1 folder 1" (Box 39)
  - Public Life (Holidays Official Ceremonies) - see 331.817 [394], 1970-2003; 59.; 1 folder 1" (Box 39)
  - Social Usage; Etiquette [395], 1957; 1975; 60.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 39)
  - Regional Integration, International & Economic [4 330.2], 1961-1998; 61.; 1 folder 1" (Box 40)
  - Regional Integration, Latin American Economic Integration [4: 330.2(132)], 1964-2002; 62.; 1 folder 1" (Box 40)
  - Regional Integration, African Economic Integration [4: 330.2(200)], 1968-2002; 63.; 1 folder 1" (Box 40)
  - Supranationalism [4 342.3], 1957-1998; 64.; 1 folder 1" (Box 40)
  - Nuclear Physics [539.1], 1966 and 1971; 65.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 379)
  - Atomic Energy [621.039], 1961-2003; 66.; 1 folder 1" (Box 390)
  - Atomic Energy, World [621.039(1)], 1966-1969; 67.; 1 folder 1" (Box 390)
  - Agriculture, World [63(1)], 1968-1993; 68.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 402)
  - Agriculture, Europe [63(20)], 1968-1998; 69.; 1 folder 0.5" (Box 402)
  - Management Theory & Practice (Europe) [65.01(20)], 1970-1985; 70.; 1 folder 1" (Box 403)
  - Business Potential in Europe for Non-European Firms [658.1(20)] (folder missing), 71. (Box 407)
  - Business Potential in the EEC for Non-EEC Firms [658.1(25)], 1960-1969; 72.; 1 folder 1" (Box 407)
  - Business Potential in European Free Trade Association (EFTA) for Non-EFTA Firms [658.1(26)] (folder missing), 73. (Box 407)
  - Companies, Europe [658.2(20)], 1968-1989; 74.; 1 folder 3" (Box 407)
  - Steel Companies [658.2(CST 67)], 1957-1963; 75.; 1 folder 1" (Box 407)
  - Marketing Studies, Miscellaneous [658.8], 1980-1990; 76.; 1 folder 2" (Box 407)
  - Advertising, General [659.1], 1968-1999; 77.; 1 folder 1" (Box 407)
  - History/Europe [93(20)], 78.; 1 folder 1" (Box 409)